

CONTACT

- +123-8082354610
- ✓ Stephaniennesochi@gmail.com
- 1 Sir Charles Ozoude Street I daw River, Enugu State, Nigeria



EDUCATION

2021 - Present GODFREY OKOYE UNIVERSITY

- Bachelor of Computer Science
- GPA: 4.5 / 5.0

SKILLS

- UI/UX design
- Project/Time Management
- Softyware developer
- Teamwork
- Product /Software Testing
- Leadership/Teamwork
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Prototyping/Wireframing
- Teaching/Tutoring

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Igbo (Fluent)
- French (Basics)

STEPHANIE EZE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER / UI/UX DESIGNER

PROFILE

I am an innovative, smart, dedicated and resilient student with qualifying skills in the areas of my interest. I give my best to what I do. I am currently indeed of a job to build myself, improve and gain more experience. I pay great attention to details and I have a year and 4 months experience in UI/UX design and 2 years experience in web development. I'm looking for a career to get me started in my career journey.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ventures Park

IT Specialist

2024 - present

- Manage the network system, ensuring efficient allocation of resources and optimizing network issues.
- · Monitor and maintain the network...
- Monitor the server room and fix issues that arise.

Home Service

2021 - 2022

Voluteer Teacher

- Tutoring and Teaching students science subjects.
- Explanation of coding concept.
- · Teaching Students on different subjects

Gbicts Academy

2020-2021

Data Entry Specislist

- Entry of clients' data into the system to arrange, edit and format.
- use of microsoft tools such as ms word, power point, excel etc. to edit clients' work.

REFERENCE

Stephanie Eze

Phone: 08082354610 / 07036171194 Email: stephaniennesochi@gmail.com